Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1880-2014 RL.01050
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal papers, 1880-2010, undated
  - Personal photographic materials, 1880-2010, undated
    - Construction of Price's rental home, 1981-1982 (Box 323)
    - Dean, James, undated (Box 325)
    - Deframed photographs from Price's home, 1900-1978, undated; 7 folders (Box 324)
      Including signed photograph of Leo Tolstoy; signed photograph of Leontyne Price; autograph of Dwight Eisenhower and MacArthur; old family photographs; a signed photographs from Toni Morrison; and, a photograph with President and Hillary Clinton with related White House correspondence.
    - Deframed photographs from Price's home, 1961-1994, undated; 6 folders (Box 326)
    - Delon, Alain, undated (Box 325)
    - Europe and United States travel, negatives, 1956-1962 (Box 318)
    - Family and friends, 1880-1929, undated (Box 310)
      Includes Elizabeth Price, William Price, family friends
    - Family and friends, 1930 - 1939 (Box 310)
      Eudora Welty; publication includes her photographs.
    - Family and friends, 1940-1949 (Box 310)
      Includes William Price and early photographs of Reynolds
    - Family and friends, 1950-1959 (Box 310)
      Includes RP's college fraternity and photographs at Duke.
    - Family and friends, 1960-1969 (Box 310)
      Includes Stephen Spender and Wallace Kaufman
    - Family and friends, 1970-1979 (Box 310)
      Includes Will Singer, Chris Beebe, and Eudora Welty
    - Family and friends, 1980-1989 (Box 310)
      Includes Bill and Memsy Price
    - Family and friends, 1990-2000; 2 folders (Box 317)
      Includes note from Memsy Price and negatives
    - Family photographs, 1900-1955 (Box 310)
      Includes William and Elizabeth Price and early photographs of RP and Bill Price.
    - Family photographs, 1947, 1948, 1995 (Box 310)
      Removed from General Correspondence 1995, Irma Walker, and, Fran Goodwin.
    - Gielgud, John, 1965 (Box 325)
      Includes signed photographs.
    - Groups, 1926-2010; 2 folders (Box 316)
      Includes Andersons; Elizabeth Price; Bill Price; and, Jordans.
    - Harris, Julie, and Price, 1990 (Box 311)
    - High school graduating class, 1951 May 26 (Box 338)
    - Holy Land travel, 1980 (Box 319)
      Includes Jeff Anderson.
    - Individuals A-K, 1933-2007; 3 folders (Box 312)
      Includes Jeff Anderson; Chris Beebe; Marcia Drake; Laird Ellis; Kevin Helliker; and, Wallace Kaufman.
    - Individuals K-V, 1926-2007; 4 folders (Box 313)
      Includes Zbigniew Pełczyński; Ross Quaintance; Eric Rector; Will Singer; Stephen Spender; and, Ann Tyler.
    - Individuals V-Z, and unidentified, 1955-2003 (Box 314)
    - Individuals and places, unidentified, 1958-1985, undated; 4 folders (Box 314)
      Includes nudes and negatives.
    - Israel, undated (Box 319)
    - Israel travel, 1983 (Box 318)
      Includes Daniel Voll.
    - Italy travel, 1980 (Box 318)
    - Japan travel, 1958-1960 (Box 319)
      Includes Shozo Tokunaga; Wallace Kaufman; and, notes from Shozo.
    - Jordan, Michael, 1955-1962 (Box 312)
      Includes photographs taken in Europe.
    - Large portraits and photographs, 1958-2006 (Box 323)
      Including Ann Taylor; Lord David Cecil; Stephen Spender; and, William Blackburn.
    - Leigh, Vivian, undated (Box 325)
    - Lyndhurst Foundation, 1994 (Box 326)
    - Macon, 1959 (Box 319)
      Includes Bill Price.
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-2001; 3 folders (Box 317)
      Includes portraits of Price, and, family photographs.
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-2008 (Box 326)
      Includes photographs of W.H. Auden.
    - Negatives, undated (Box 322)
    - Negatives, black and white safety film, undated; 6 folders (Box 327)
      Includes unidentified subjects.
    - Negatives, black and white safety film, undated; 5 folders (Box 328)
    - Negatives from Clear Pictures, undated (Box 327)
    - Negatives, color negatives, undated; 5 folders (Box 329)
    - Negatives, nitrates, #1-203, undated; 3 folders (Box 351)
      Includes early (1930s) Price family photographs used in Guggenheim exhibit in 1991. Includes folder of negatives marked Duplicates, and "Bad" Negatives.
    - Negatives, nitrates, #203-453, undated; 6 folders (Box 352)
      Includes early (1930s) Price family photographs, used in Guggenheim exhibit in 1991. Notes with identification of photographs in envelope #321. Notes included in other negative sleeves in Folder 8.
    - North Carolina, 1959 (Box 319)
    - Nudes, undated (Box 326)
    - Original art, 1915, 1954 (Box 317)
    - Oxford, 1956-1957; 2 folders (Box 319)
      Includes John Anderson, and, Stephen Spender.
    - Oxford, Europe, USA travel, 1956 (Box 319)
    - Pełczyński, Zbigniew, 1958 (Box 313)
    - Personal photographs, assorted, 1923-1951 (Box 289)
      Includes newspaper photograph of Price; Mary Ann Powell; and Lauritz Melchior; and Shirley Habel; portrait of John Egerton Rowan; and, photographs taken in Asheboro.
    - Places, 1920-2004 (Box 318)
      Includes photographs of Price's father's home; Europe; and, Duke University.
    - Places, large print, 1950, undated (Box 318)
      Includes Duke University.
    - Portrait at Merton College, Oxford, 1956 (Box 354)
      Includes a list of those in photograph, including Michael Jordan.
    - Portrait of freshman, Matriculation Day at Merton College, 1955 (Box 353)
    - Portrait of Phi Delta Theta at Duke, 1953 (Box 354)
      Contains list of members.
    - Portraits of Price, 1958-1996; 4 folders (Box 321)
      Including graduation pictures.
    - Portrait of Red Dawn, 1980 (Box 347)
      From Camp Sequoyah.
    - President Richard Brodhead Inauguration Panel: Duke Past, Present and Future, 2004-09-18 (Box 349)
      Poster is gift from Nancy Bates Allen; features John Hope Franklin, Nancy Bates Allen, Stanley Hamerwas, and Mike Krzyzewski
    - Price, 1933-2009 (Box 323)
      Including Price at home.
    - Price and friends, 1961 (Box 317)
    - Price and friends from Europe, 1956-1959; 2 folders (Box 319)
      Includes Zbigniew Pełczyński, and, Michael Jordan.
    - Price and groups, 1934-2008; 3 folders (Box 315)
      Includes Stephen Spender; cast of New Music Trilogy; Duke English Department; and, Ann Taylor.
    - Price and groups, large print, 1963-2001; 3 folders (Box 315)
      Includes Price receiving Sir Walter Raleigh Award.
    - Price at home, 1968-2001 (Box 323)
    - Price, Leontyne, 1960-1970 (Box 325)
    - Price portraits, 1955-2008; 2 folders (Box 322)
      Includes Price at Duke.
    - Price portraits, 1985 (Box 323)
    - Price portraits, large, 1923-1994 (Box 289)
    - Price portraits with actors and friends, 1961-2000 (Box 322)
      Includes Wallace Kaufman; Will Singer; Frank Hielema; and, Eduardo Morel.
    - Price with individuals, 1934-2003; 2 folders (Box 311)
      Includes artist Jacob Collins; Polly Holliday; Bill Price; Elizabeth Price; William Price; and, Eudora Welty.
    - Price and unidentified people, undated (Box 315)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 322)
    - Publicity photographs, 1993-1996 (Box 322)
    - Rodwells and Drakes, 1924 (Box 310)
    - Spender, Stephen, 1938-1993 (Box 313)
    - Spender, Stephen, portrait by Imogen Cunningham, 1959 (Box 347)
    - Styron, William, and Price, 1978 (Box 311)
    - Surface of the Earth, 1973 (Box 325)
      Photographs by Duane Michaels in Esquire magazine.
    - Taylor, James, at Newport Folk Festival, 1969 (Box 353)
    - Travel, United States, 1960 (Box 319)
    - Welty, Eudora, 1955-1984 (Box 314)
      Includes first signed photo Welty gave to Price.
    - Welty, Eudora, photograph of Abandoned "Lunatic Asylum", 1976 (Box 354)
    - West Coast: California, Montana, Wyoming, 1965 (Box 318)
      Includes Garfeins and Carroll Baker.
    - Price and writing class, 1991,1999 (Box 315)
    - Stryrer, Jim, undated (Box 325)
    - Various artists, undated (Box 325)
    - Weismuller, Johnny, undated (Box 325)
    - Welty, Eudora, undated (Box 289)
  - Photograph albums and scrapbooks, 1904-1952, undated
    This subseries includes family photographs albums and scrapbooks, and is arranged chronologically.
    - Scrapbooks, early family photographs, RP baby book, autograph album, 1904-1943, undated; 3 items (Box 284)
      Autographs album includes original signatures from celebrities and government officials including, Bing Crosby; Harry James; Kay Kyser; Jack Dempsey; Mark W. Clark; Ira C. Eaker; Barbara Stanwyck; Gene Krupa; Gregory Peck; and, June Allyson.
    - Family photographs, RP portraits, Phi Delta Theta Fraternity, 1918, 1923-1994, undated; 13 folders (Box 289)
      Includes event photographs. Photographs of Eudora Welty, John Burton Rodwell, Barbara Dearing Howe, Arturo Toscanini, Kirsten Flagstad, and unidentified.
    - Scrapbook, family pictures, clippings, and letters, 1933-1951, undated (Box 278)
    - Scrapbook, family pictures, childhood drawings, 1938-1943, undated (Box 283)
    - Scrapbook, family pictures, 1939-1952, undated (Box 279)
    - Scrapbooks, feature Ingrid Bergman; Jennifer Jones; and, Vivien Leigh, 1943, 1945, 1948, undated (Box 287)
      Includes movie stills from Song of Bernadette; Joan of Arc; Caesar and Cleopatra; and, Anna Karenina.
    - Scrapbooks, features Ingrid Bergman; and, Vivien Leigh, 1948, 1949, undated (Box 286)
      Includes movie stills from Spellbound; Joan of Arc; and, Gone With The Wind.
    - Scrapbook, opera and theater, 1948-1951, undated (Box 282)
      Includes clippings of opera and theater reviews, copies of Playbill, and signed celebrity headshots. Marian Anderson is featured.
    - Scrapbook, features Ingrid Bergman and Vivien Leigh, 1949, 1951, undated (Box 285)
      Includes Playbills and Metropolitan Opera programs.
    - Scrapbook, cinema and theater, 1950-1952, undated (Box 281)
      Includes clippings of film and theater reviews, copies of Playbills, signed celebrity headshots, and RP's ticket stubs. Marlon Brando and Vivien Leigh are featured.
    - Scrapbook, Duke University, family pictures, and clippings, 1951-1952, undated (Box 280)
    - Photographic album of portraits, including Abraham Lincoln, undated (Box 343)
  - Price as student and teacher, 1955-2008
    Materials in this subseries reflect Price's work as a professor, and are arranged chronologically.
    - University Archives photographs, 1955, 1968, 1975 (Box 307)
      Includes photographs of Price as a student and a teacher.
    - Bread on the Waters: Reynolds Price, Teacher, a documentary by Wil Weldon, 1997 (Box 307)
    - Weekend with Reynolds Price, 2001 (Box 307)
    - Duke Alumni Affairs, 2002 (Box 307)
    - Price biography, 2002, undated (Box 307)
    - Reynolds Price, 50 Years A Teacher, 2007 (Box 309)
      A commemorative book including letters and clippings.
    - Jubilee for Reynolds Price, 2008 (Box 307)
    - Bread on the Waters: Reynolds Price, Teacher, a documentary by Wil Weldon, 2001; 1 Files wmv file; 83 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Includes excerpt from video used for a 2001 exhibit.
  - Private Correspondence, 1935-1979, undated
    Includes correspondence and documents Price kept in a locked box in his home, and is arranged chronologically.
    - Price family, 1935, 1945-1952, undated (Box 269)
      Includes photographs of Price as a child.
    - Spender, Stephen, 1957-1961, 1965-1967, 1979, undated; 3 folders (Box 269)
      Includes correspondence from Price to Stephen Spender.
    - Pełczyński, Zbigniew, 1958-1959, undated (Box 269)
    - Unidentified correspondent, 1959 (Box 269)
    - Spender family, 1970, undated (Box 269)
    - Closed correspondence note, undated (Box 269)
- Events, 1949-2009, undated
  This Series includes materials announcing, advertising, or describing addresses, appearances, performances, conferences, and speeches, attended by Price as either a participant or audience member.
  - Printed materials, 1949-2009, undated
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1993-2003; 2 folders (Box 331)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1994 (Box 289)
    - Announcements and programs for author appearances: addresses, conferences, readings, and other engagements, 1962-2004, undated; 7 folders (Box 331)
    - Announcements and programs for author appearances: addresses, conferences, readings, and other engagements, 1962-2004, undated; 2 folders (Box 332)
    - Announcements and programs for events attended: concerts, plays, services, and other occasions, 1949-2006, undated; 7 folders (Box 332)
    - Announcements and programs for events attended: concerts, plays, services, and other occasions, 1949-2004, undated; 2 folders (Box 333)
    - An Appalachian Summer, 2000 (Box 333)
    - An Evening with Southern Writers, poster, 1993 Nov 4 (Box 347)
      Signed by students and staff from the Demensions Project.
    - Awards and honorary degrees, 1964-2003, undated; 4 folders (Box 333)
    - Catalogs and brochures with writings by Price, 1999, undated (Box 333)
    - Duke University events, 1988-2004, undated (Box 333)
    - Eudora Welty Foundation, 1999-2008, undated; 2 folders (Box 333)
    - Events featuring and/or hosted by Price, 2004-2006 (Box 334)
    - Fellowship of Southern Writers, 1989-2008, undated (Box 334)
    - Halloween 2000, 2000 Oct 31; 1 Files 1 MS Word file; 19 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Includes list of readings.
    - Invitations, 1993-2003, undated (Box 334)
    - Invitations to events, 1993-2009 (Box 334)
    - Lincoln Center Theater review, 2008 Fall (Box 334)
      New Treasure by Price.
    - Magazines, 2008 (Box 334)
      Garden and Gun
    - Miscellany, 1944-2001; 8 folders (Box 337)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1990 (Box 350)
      Includes A Long and Happy Life Poster, South Carolina Writers Series poster
    - National Book Award Week, 1979 Apr 23-26 (Box 334)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1999, 2005, undated (Box 334)
    - NC Writers Network, 2004 (Box 334)
      20th Anniversary Fall Conference
    - Oxford University printed material, 1954-1962, undated (Box 334)
    - Plays, 1957, undated (Box 334)
      includes signature of Leonard Bernstein
    - Playbills and tickets, 2000 (Box 334)
    - Poster for Salem College for Center of Women Writers' National Literary Competitions, 2006 (Box 168)
      Description for Reynolds Price Short Fiction Award
    - Postcards, hotel brochures, Nasher Art Museum exhibit, undated (Box 334)
    - Programs and announcements for Price's plays, 1956-2003, undated; 2 folders (Box 334)
    - Publications by various authors (alphabetical), 1959-1995, undated (Box 334)
    - Publications by various authors (alphabetical), 1959-1995, undated; 4 folders (Box 335)
    - Publishers' ads, catalogs, and prospecti, 1966-2000, undated; 7 folders (Box 335)
    - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1975-1977, undated (Box 336)
    - Song: From so Far written for the American Academy of Arts and Letters by Price and Morton Gould, undated (Box 347)
      includes art from unknown
    - Spender family printed material, 1959-1977, undated (Box 336)
    - Taylor, James, 1992-2001; 5 folders (Box 336)
    - Van Cliburn International Piano Competition, 1993-1994; 4 folders (Box 336)
  - Recordings of Reynolds Price's events, 1981-2000, undated
    - Fortieth Reunion, 1951-1991 (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0009)
    - Price and Wallace Kaufman - Jessie Rehder, Anne Tyler, 1964 Aug 14, 1974 Nov 14 (Box 299, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0091)
    - Interview #1 with Reynolds Price Southern Writers Project, 1973 Jun 18 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0001)
    - Jim Boatwright and Stephen Spender, 1974 Feb 15-17 (Box 299, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0092)
    - Price at Baylor School, 1975 Apr (Box 299, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0093)
    - Interview #4 with Reynolds Price, Southern Writers Project, 1975 Jun 8 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0004)
    - Price at Broughton English Department, 1975 Aug 15 (Box 299, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0094)
    - Eudora Welty, Duke Reading, 1977 March-1978 Feb (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0134)
    - First & Third Lectures in Salzburg, 1977 June (Box 299, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0095)
    - Reynolds Price reading, Salzburg Seminar, 1977 June (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0097)
    - Today Show, visit to Statesville, 1975 July 23- 1976 May 11 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0122)
    - Golden Hours, Blue Calhoun, R. Vaughn, 1979 Mar 5-1992 May 15 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0111)
    - The Dick Cavett Show, All Things Considered, 1981 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0125)
    - Dick Cavett Show, 1981 June 3 (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0017)
    - The Dick Cavett Show, 1981 Jun 6 (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0014)
    - Interviews with Roger Sauls, 1983 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0127)
    - Dave Smith, reading his poems, 1984 Feb 27 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0149)
    - Reynolds Price on PBS's Heat, 1989 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0151)
    - A Special Weekend at Duke University, 1989 Feb 9-11 (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0002)
    - A Special Weekend at Duke, 1989 Feb 9-11 (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0015)
    - Celebration for the Right Rev. Paul Moore Jr., 1989 June 11 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0137)
    - North Carolina People UNC Center for Public TV, 1990 July 26 (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0005)
    - Reynolds Price on Fresh Air, 1990 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0108)
    - Reynolds Price on NPR's Heat with John Hockenberry, 1990 Aug 30 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0109)
    - Reynold Price's Y reading, 1990 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0107)
    - Reynolds Price in Duke Chapel, Library Celebration, 1991 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0110)
    - Writers Reading, 1991 Nov (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0020)
    - Reynolds Price on Bookworm, 1992 June 8 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0152)
    - FOL dinner: Bill & Reynolds Price Meredith College, 1996 Mar 25 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0015)
    - Bookworm: Michael Silverblatt interviews Reynold Price on biblical translation and Three Gospels, 1996 Jun 20 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0016)
    - Lenten Meditation and Music: Duke Chapel, Reynolds Price performs biblical reading, 1997 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0019)
    - Lenten Meditation and Music: Duke Chapel, 1997 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0023)
    - Lenten Meditation and Music: Duke Chapel, 1997 (Box 291, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0043)
    - Public Interest Reynolds Price, 1998 June 29 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0128)
    - North Caroliniana Society Award Banquet Honoring Reynolds Price, 1999 April 9; 4 items (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0015 - RL01050-VHS-0016)
    - North Caroliniana Society Award Banquet Honoring Reynolds Price, 1999 April 9; 2 items (Box 295, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0008 - RL01050-Bcam-0009)
    - North Caroliniana Society Award Banquet Honoring Reynolds Price, 1999 April 9; 2 items (Box 298, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0033 - RL01050-VHS-0034)
    - The Friday Night Women's Read, 2000 Feb (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0129)
    - Price and Charlie Rose, 2008 Jan 31; 4 items (Box 296, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0029 - RL01050-Bcam-0032)
      Price and Charlie Rose, 2 tapes from 2 cameras
    - American Audio Prose Library Reynolds Price Interview, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0130)
    - American Audio Prose Library, undated (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0112)
    - A Special Weekend at Duke University, undated (Box 297, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0014)
    - Book Show Reynolds Price, undated (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0114)
    - Christmas in Duke Chapel, undated (Box 295, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0001)
    - Christmas in Duke Chapel, undated (Box 294, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0024)
    - Christmas in Duke Chapel, undated (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0002)
    - The Dick Cavett Show, undated (Box 295, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0007)
    - The Duke Endowment 75th Anniversary Symposium Video, undated (Box 294, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0025)
    - The Duke Endowment, undated (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0012)
    - The Duke Endowment, undated (Box 297, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0023)
    - FOL Dinner, Meredith College: Bill & Reynolds Price, undated (Box 291, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0038)
    - FOL Dinner, Meredith College: Bill & Reynolds Price, undated (Box 292, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0061)
    - Interview #2 with Reynolds Price Southern Writers Project, undated (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0002)
    - Oral History #27 Southern Writers, Price, undated (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0003)
    - Reynolds Price NYU, undated (Box 294, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0029)
    - The Sound of Writing Program #27, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0120)
    - untitled, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0133)
    - untitled, undated (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0018)
    - Writers Reading, undated (Box 297, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0017)
    - The Writers Workshop, undated (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0006)
    - The Writers Workshop, undated (Box 296, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0013)
    - The Writers Workshop Reynolds Price benefit reading, undated (Box 294, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0031)
  - Photographs, 1960-2007
    - Social gatherings, 1960-2000 (Box 330)
    - 6th Annual Eudora Welty Americana Awards, 1976 (Box 330)
      Photographs of Price teaching.
    - Organized events, 1982-2001; 2 folders (Box 330)
    - Negatives, 1994-1997 (Box 330)
      Broughton High School Reunion
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, group photographs, 2000 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Danny Robinette Show, 2001 (Box 330)
      Curated by Reynolds Price
    - Price's 50th High School Reunion, 2001 (Box 330)
    - Perkins Library Exhibit, 2001 (Box 330)
    - Price Lecture, 2007 October (Box 330)
      Thomas Wolfe Lecture at UNC Chapel Hill
- Duke University, 1960-2010, undated
  This Series includes documents relating to Price's professorship at Duke University, and material is arranged alphabetically or chronologically.
  RESTRICTIONS: Items in this subseries are restricted until 2079 under FERPA rules.
  - Business, 1960-2010, undated
    - Duke Correspondence, 1960, 1972-1999, 2000-2010, undated; 3 folders (Box 301)
    - Duke correspondence, electronic documents, 1992, 2000-2005, undated; 32 Files 32 MS Word and text files; 2 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Includes correspondence, emails, and memoranda relating to Duke department programming; faculty, hiring; recommendations; and, salaries.
    - Inauguration of Nannerl Overholser Keohane, 1993 (Box 301)
    - Trustee/Faculty Committee on honorary degrees, 2006-2007; 2 folders (Box 301)
    - University strategic plan, 2006 (Box 301)
    - William M. Blackburn Fund, 1972-1994, 2003-2010, undated (Box 301)
  - Course Notes and Schedules, 1962-2008, undated
    - Class and exam schedules, 1969, 1982-1993, 2005 (Box 303)
    - Course materials, 1962-2009, undated; 2 folders (Box 303)
    - Course materials, electronic, 1992, 1996-2005, undated; 20 Files 20 MS Word and text files; 600 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Includes course syllabi; exam questions; and, notes.
    - Notes on Milton, 2001, 2008, undated (Box 303)
    - Notes on Milton, undated; 3 folders (Box 303)
      Includes index cards of notes on Milton.
  - Students, 1990-2009, undated
    This subseries includes Price's diagrams of student seating, and selected writing by students.
    - Duke course seating, 2008-2009, undated (Box 308)
    - Students' enrollment, proposals, and references, 1993-2007 (Box 308)
    - Students' writing, 1990-2009, undated; 3 folders (Box 308)
  - Recordings of Price at Duke, 1973-2006, undated
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - Readings and discussions, 1973 Nov 30, Dec 6 (Box 299, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0089)